Hula, Erich; Papers ger044
M.E. Grenander Department of Special Collections & Archives
- Published and Unpublished Writings by Erich Hula, 1924-1984; 3; 288 file folders
  - Writings, primarily in English; reviews, 1939-1984; 3.2; 204 file folders
    - Nationalism and Internationalism: European and American Perspectives, 1984; 3.2.76 (Box 5 (3-Published and Unpublished Writings by ), Folder 22-28)
      - University Press of America. Correspondence concerning publication of book (Box 5 (3.2.76-Nationalism and Internationalism: European and Ame), Folder 27)
      - Thompson, Kenneth W. Correspondence, 1980-1984 (Box 5 (3.2.76-Nationalism and Internationalism: European and Ame), Folder 28)
    - Reviews by Erich Hula, 1924-1984; 3.2.77 (Box 5 (3-Published and Unpublished Writings by ), Folder 29-150)
      - Nawiasky, Hans.Die Zukunft der politischen Parteien, 1924 (Box 5 (3.2.77-Reviews by Erich Hula), Folder 29)
      - Koellreutter, Otto.Die politischen Parteien im modernen Staate, 1926 (Box 5 (3.2.77-Reviews by Erich Hula), Folder 30)
      - von den Steinen, Wolfram.Heilige und Helden des Mittelalters, 1926 (Box 5 (3.2.77-Reviews by Erich Hula), Folder 31)
      - Müller-Meinigen, Ernst.Parlamentarismus. Betrachtungen, Lehren und Erinnerungen aus deutschen Parlamenten, 1927 (Box 5 (3.2.77-Reviews by Erich Hula), Folder 32)
      - Sait, E. M.American Parties and Elections, 1927 (Box 5 (3.2.77-Reviews by Erich Hula), Folder 33)
      - Heller, Hermann.Die politische Ideenkrise der Gegenwart, 1927 (Box 5 (3.2.77-Reviews by Erich Hula), Folder 34)
      - Bernhard, Hasn Anton.Das parlamentarische Wahlrecht, 1927 (Box 5 (3.2.77-Reviews by Erich Hula), Folder 35)
      - Schlesinger, Martin Ludwig.Das bolschewistische Rußland, 1927 (Box 5 (3.2.77-Reviews by Erich Hula), Folder 36)
      - Michels, Robert.Bedeutende Männer. Charakterologische Studien, 1927 (Box 5 (3.2.77-Reviews by Erich Hula), Folder 37)
      - Michels, Robert.Soziologie als Gesellschaftswissenschaft, 1927 (Box 5 (3.2.77-Reviews by Erich Hula), Folder 38)
      - Michels, Robert.Sittlichkeit in Ziffern? Kritik der Moralstatistik, 1928 (Box 5 (3.2.77-Reviews by Erich Hula), Folder 39)
      - Michels, Robert.Die Verelendungstheorie. Studien und Untersuchungen zur internationalen Dogmengeschichte der Volkswirtschaft, 1928 (Box 5 (3.2.77-Reviews by Erich Hula), Folder 40)
      - Aris, Reinhold.Die Staatslehre Adam Müllers in ihrem Verhältnis zur deutschen Romantik, 1929 (Box 5 (3.2.77-Reviews by Erich Hula), Folder 41)
      - Aulard, A. et B. Mirkine-Guetzévitch.Les déclarations des droits de l'homme, 1929 (Box 5 (3.2.77-Reviews by Erich Hula), Folder 42)
      - Herring, E. P.Group Representation before Congress, 1929 (Box 5 (3.2.77-Reviews by Erich Hula), Folder 43)
      - Hedlam-Morley, Agnes.The new democratic constitutions of Europe, 1929 (Box 5 (3.2.77-Reviews by Erich Hula), Folder 44)
      - Kantorowicz, Hermann.Der Geist der evangelischen Politik und das Gespenst der Einkreisung Deutschlands, 1929 (Box 5 (3.2.77-Reviews by Erich Hula), Folder 45)
      - Kircher, Rudolf.Wie's die Engländer machen. Politik, Gesellschaft und Literatur im demokratisierten England, 1929 (Box 5 (3.2.77-Reviews by Erich Hula), Folder 46)
      - Michels, Robert.Der Patriotismus. Prolegomena zu seiner soziologischen Analyse, 1929 (Box 5 (3.2.77-Reviews by Erich Hula), Folder 47)
      - Mirkine-Getzewitsch, B.Die Rechtstheoretischen Grundlagen des Sowjetstaates, 1929 (Box 5 (3.2.77-Reviews by Erich Hula), Folder 48)
      - Der Geist der englischen Politik und das Gespenst der Einkreisung Deutschlands, 1930 (Box 5 (3.2.77-Reviews by Erich Hula), Folder 49)
      - Alessandri, Arturo.Parlementarisme et Régime Présidentiel. Evolution constitutionelle, internationale, financière et sociale du Chili, 1930 (Box 5 (3.2.77-Reviews by Erich Hula), Folder 50)
      - Irwin, Will.Herbert Hoover. Biographische Erinnerungen, 1930 (Box 5 (3.2.77-Reviews by Erich Hula), Folder 51)
      - Koellreutter, Otto.Der englisches Staat der Gegenwart und das britische Weltreich, 1930 (Box 5 (3.2.77-Reviews by Erich Hula), Folder 52)
      - Lambert, Jacques.Histoire Constitutionelle de l'Union Américaine, 1930 (Box 5 (3.2.77-Reviews by Erich Hula), Folder 53)
      - Huber, Ernst Rudolf.Das Deutsche Reich als Wirtschaftsstaat, 1931 (Box 5 (3.2.77-Reviews by Erich Hula), Folder 54)
      - Métall, R.A.Das Schrifttum zur österreichischen Bundesverfassung, 1920-1930, 1931 (Box 5 (3.2.77-Reviews by Erich Hula), Folder 55)
      - Mirkine-Guetzévitch, B.Les Constitutions de l'Europe Nouvelle, 1930 (Box 5 (3.2.77-Reviews by Erich Hula), Folder 56)
      - Ribbeck, Hans Georg von.Kaiser, Reichspräsident und U.S.A.-Präsident, 1930 (Box 5 (3.2.77-Reviews by Erich Hula), Folder 57)
      - Jennings, W. Ivor.Principles of Local Government Law, 1931 (Box 5 (3.2.77-Reviews by Erich Hula), Folder 58)
      - Mirkine-Guetzévitch, B.Les Nouvelles Tendances du Droit Constitutionnel, 1931 (Box 5 (3.2.77-Reviews by Erich Hula), Folder 59)
      - Feiler, Arthur.Das Experiment des Bolschewismus, 1931 (Box 5 (3.2.77-Reviews by Erich Hula), Folder 60)
      - Fleiner, Fritz.Unitarismus und Föderalismus in der Schweiz und in den Vereinigten Staaten von Amerika, 1931 (Box 5 (3.2.77-Reviews by Erich Hula), Folder 61)
      - Schlottmann, Rudolf.Die Verfassungen Englands, Nordamerikas, Frankreichs, der Schweiz, Deutschlands in objektiver Darstellung, deutschen Verfassungstexten und ausländischer Kritik, 1931 (Box 5 (3.2.77-Reviews by Erich Hula), Folder 62)
      - Kaisenberg, Georg.Die Wahl zum Reichstag. Führer für die Reichstagswahlen, 1931 (Box 5 (3.2.77-Reviews by Erich Hula), Folder 63)
      - Lötschert, Hugo.Der Völkerbund im Unterricht; Der Volkerbund, 1931 (Box 5 (3.2.77-Reviews by Erich Hula), Folder 64)
      - Röder, Hans Fritz.Parteien und Parteienstaat in Deutschland, 1931 (Box 5 (3.2.77-Reviews by Erich Hula), Folder 65)
      - van Calker, Fritz.Wesen und Sinn der politischen Parteien, 1931 (Box 5 (3.2.77-Reviews by Erich Hula), Folder 66)
      - Braunias, Karl.Das parlamentaische Wahlrecht, 1932 (Box 5 (3.2.77-Reviews by Erich Hula), Folder 67)
      - Beer, Max.Die Reise nach Genf, 1932 (Box 5 (3.2.77-Reviews by Erich Hula), Folder 68)
      - Académie de droit international, 1932 (Box 5 (3.2.77-Reviews by Erich Hula), Folder 69)
      - Emerson, Rupert.State and Sovereignty in Modern Germany, 1932 (Box 5 (3.2.77-Reviews by Erich Hula), Folder 70)
      - Das parlamentarische Wahlrecht, 1933 (Box 5 (3.2.77-Reviews by Erich Hula), Folder 71)
      - Bibliothèque de l'Institut International de Droit Public, 1933 (Box 5 (3.2.77-Reviews by Erich Hula), Folder 72)
      - La Vie Juridique des Peuples, 1933 (Box 5 (3.2.77-Reviews by Erich Hula), Folder 73)
      - Bavaj, Amor.Il Principio Rappresentativo nella Stato Sovietico, 1934 (Box 5 (3.2.77-Reviews by Erich Hula), Folder 74)
      - Eschmann, Ernst Wilhelm.Der faschistische Staat in Italien, 1934 (Box 5 (3.2.77-Reviews by Erich Hula), Folder 75)
      - Matthias, Eugen.Amerikas Schicksal. Beobachtungen und Voraussagen eines Biologen im Hinblick auf europäische Verhältnisse, 1934 (Box 5 (3.2.77-Reviews by Erich Hula), Folder 76)
      - Mazzoni, Giuliano.L'Ordinamento Corporativo; Bartolotto, Guido. Politica Corporativa, 1934 (Box 5 (3.2.77-Reviews by Erich Hula), Folder 77)
      - Paresce, Enrico. Giorgio Sorel ed altri saggi, 1934 (Box 5 (3.2.77-Reviews by Erich Hula), Folder 78)
      - Pergolesi, Ferruccio.Istituzioni di Diritto Corporativo, 1934 (Box 5 (3.2.77-Reviews by Erich Hula), Folder 79)
      - Schmitz, Hans.Die Sozialpolitik im autoritären Staat, 1934 (Box 5 (3.2.77-Reviews by Erich Hula), Folder 80)
      - Schmitz, Richard.Der Weg zur berufsständischen Ordnung in Österreich, 1934 (Box 5 (3.2.77-Reviews by Erich Hula), Folder 81)
      - Weichs, Friedrich Freiherr von.Wie bauen wir den Ständesstaat?, 1934 (Box 5 (3.2.77-Reviews by Erich Hula), Folder 82)
      - Zahn, Johannes C.D.Wirtschaftsführertum und Vertragsethik im neuen Aktienrecht, 1934 (Box 5 (3.2.77-Reviews by Erich Hula), Folder 83)
      - Fanno, Marco.Introduzione allo Studio della Teoria Economica del Corporativismo, 1935 (Box 5 (3.2.77-Reviews by Erich Hula), Folder 84)
      - Hiller, Carl.Die Grundlagen des faschistischen Staates; Pitigliani, Fausto. The Italian Corporative State, 1935 (Box 5 (3.2.77-Reviews by Erich Hula), Folder 85)
      - Mangoldt, Hermann.Geschriebene Verfassung und Rechtssicherheit in den Vereinigten Staaten von Amerika, 1935 (Box 5 (3.2.77-Reviews by Erich Hula), Folder 86)
      - Menzel, Adolf. Der Staatsgedanke des Fascismus. Eine geistesgeschichtliche Untersuchung, 1935 (Box 5 (3.2.77-Reviews by Erich Hula), Folder 87)
      - Meriggi, Lea.Faschismus und Recht, 1935 (Box 5 (3.2.77-Reviews by Erich Hula), Folder 88)
      - Nawiasky, Hans.Rechtsfragen des wirtschaftlichen Neuaufbaues, 1935 (Box 5 (3.2.77-Reviews by Erich Hula), Folder 89)
      - Savelkouls, Hermann.Das englische Kabinettsystem, 1935 (Box 5 (3.2.77-Reviews by Erich Hula), Folder 90)
      - Schramm, Edmund.Donoso Cortés. Leben und Werk eines spanischen Antiliberalen, 1935 (Box 5 (3.2.77-Reviews by Erich Hula), Folder 91)
      - Zanobini, Guido.Corso di Diritto Corporativo, 1935 (Box 5 (3.2.77-Reviews by Erich Hula), Folder 92)
      - Bagolini, Luigi.La Prima e la Seconda Dichiarazione della Carta del Lavoro, 1937 (Box 5 (3.2.77-Reviews by Erich Hula), Folder 93)
      - Romano, Edmondo.Le fonti e gli organi del diritto sindacale italiano; Benedetti, Ugo. Gli aspetti della nozione di 'azienda-impresa' nell'ordine corporativo, 1937 (Box 5 (3.2.77-Reviews by Erich Hula), Folder 94)
      - Venditti, Carlo.Principii di Diritto Corporativo, 1937 (Box 5 (3.2.77-Reviews by Erich Hula), Folder 95)
      - I 10 Anni della Carta del Lavoro, 1938 (Box 5 (3.2.77-Reviews by Erich Hula), Folder 96)
      - Asanger, Raimund.Beiträge zur Lehre vom Rechtsstaat im 19. Jahrhundert, 1938 (Box 5 (3.2.77-Reviews by Erich Hula), Folder 97)
      - Jöhr, Adolf Walter.Die ständische Ordnung. Geschichte, Idee und Neuaufbau, 1938 (Box 5 (3.2.77-Reviews by Erich Hula), Folder 98)
      - Jennings, W. Ivor.Parliament, 1940 (Box 5 (3.2.77-Reviews by Erich Hula), Folder 99)
      - Steiner, Arthur H.Government in Fascist Italy, 1941 (Box 5 (3.2.77-Reviews by Erich Hula), Folder 100)
      - Schuman, Frederick L.Night Over Europe. The Diplomacy of Nemesis, 1939-1940, 1941 (Box 5 (3.2.77-Reviews by Erich Hula), Folder 101)
      - Hudson, Manley O.International Tribunals, Past and Future, 1944 (Box 5 (3.2.77-Reviews by Erich Hula), Folder 102)
      - Kohn, Hans.The Idea of Nationalism. A Study in its Origins and Background, 1944 (Box 5 (3.2.77-Reviews by Erich Hula), Folder 103)
      - Colegrove, Kenneth.The American Senate and World Peace, 1945 (Box 5 (3.2.77-Reviews by Erich Hula), Folder 104)
      - Timasheff, Nicholas S.The Great Retreat, 1946 (Box 5 (3.2.77-Reviews by Erich Hula), Folder 105)
      - Schechtman, Joseph B.European Population Transfers 1939-1945, 1946 (Box 5 (3.2.77-Reviews by Erich Hula), Folder 106)
      - Binkley, Wilfred E.President and Congress, 1947 (Box 5 (3.2.77-Reviews by Erich Hula), Folder 107)
      - Goodrich, Leland M. and Edvard Hambro.Charter of the United Nations. Commentary and Documents, 1947 (Box 5 (3.2.77-Reviews by Erich Hula), Folder 108)
      - Glueck, Sheldon.The Nuremberg Trial and Aggressive War, 1947 (Box 5 (3.2.77-Reviews by Erich Hula), Folder 109)
      - Jessup, Philip C.A Modern Law of Nations. An Introduction, 1948 (Box 5 (3.2.77-Reviews by Erich Hula), Folder 110)
      - Kulischer, Eugene M.Europe on the Move. War and Population Changes, 1917-47, 1948 (Box 5 (3.2.77-Reviews by Erich Hula), Folder 111)
      - Journey for Our Time. The Journals of the Marquis de Custine, 1951 (Box 5 (3.2.77-Reviews by Erich Hula), Folder 112)
      - Kennan, George F.American Diplomacy, 1900-1950, 1951 (Box 5 (3.2.77-Reviews by Erich Hula), Folder 112a)
      - Mirkine-Guetzévitch, Boris.Les Constitutions Européennes, 1952 (Box 5 (3.2.77-Reviews by Erich Hula), Folder 113)
      - Smal-Stocki, Roman.The Nationality Problem of the Soviet Union and Russian Communist Imperialism, 1953 (Box 5 (3.2.77-Reviews by Erich Hula), Folder 114)
      - Kohn, Hans.Pan-Slavism: Its History and Ideology, 1953 (Box 5 (3.2.77-Reviews by Erich Hula), Folder 115)
      - Hiscocks, Richard.The Rebirth of Austria, 1954 (Box 5 (3.2.77-Reviews by Erich Hula), Folder 116)
      - Carr, Edward Hallett.The Bolshevik Revolution, 1917-1923 (Box 5 (3.2.77-Reviews by Erich Hula), Folder 117)
      - Gurian, Waldemar (ed.).Soviet Imperialism - Its Origins and Tactics: A Symposium, 1954 (Box 5 (3.2.77-Reviews by Erich Hula), Folder 117)
      - Van Langenhove, Fernand.La Crise du Systeme de Securite Colletive des Nations Unies 1946-1957, 1958 (Box 5 (3.2.77-Reviews by Erich Hula), Folder 118)
      - Die Internationale Politik 1955. Eine Einführung in das Geschehen der Gegenwart. Ed. Arnold Bergstraesser and Wilhelm Cornides, 1959 (Box 5 (3.2.77-Reviews by Erich Hula), Folder 119)
      - Graham, Robert A.Vatican Diplomacy. A Study of Church and State on the International Plane, 1959 (Box 5 (3.2.77-Reviews by Erich Hula), Folder 120)
      - Berber, Friedrich.Lehrbuch des Völkerrechts. I: Allgemeines Friedensrecht, 1960 (Box 5 (3.2.77-Reviews by Erich Hula), Folder 121)
      - Brecht, Arnold.Political Theory. The Foundations of Twentieth-Century Political Thought, 1960 (Box 5 (3.2.77-Reviews by Erich Hula), Folder 122)
      - Diamant, Alfred.Austrian Catholics and the First Republic. Democracy, Capitalism and the Social Order, 1918-1934, 1960 (Box 5 (3.2.77-Reviews by Erich Hula), Folder 123)
      - Herz, John H.International Politics in the Atomic Age, 1960 (Box 5 (3.2.77-Reviews by Erich Hula), Folder 124)
      - Niebuhr, Reinhold.The Structure of Nations and Empires, 1960/1961 (Box 5 (3.2.77-Reviews by Erich Hula), Folder 125)
      - Goodman, Elliot R.The Soviet Design for a World State, 1961 (Box 5 (3.2.77-Reviews by Erich Hula), Folder 126)
      - Völkerrecht und rechtliches Weltbild. Festschrift für Alfred Verdross, 1962 (Box 5 (3.2.77-Reviews by Erich Hula), Folder 127)
      - Clute, Robert E.The International Legal Status of Austria 1938-1955, 1962 (Box 5 (3.2.77-Reviews by Erich Hula), Folder 128)
      - Ermacora, Felix.Der Minderheitenschutz in der Arbeit der Vereinten Nationen, 1964 (Box 5 (3.2.77-Reviews by Erich Hula), Folder 129)
      - Staatslexikon. Recht, Wirtschaft, Gesellschaft, 1962-1971 (Box 5 (3.2.77-Reviews by Erich Hula), Folder 130)
      - Kelsen, Hans.Reine Rechtslehre. Mit einem Anhang: Das Problem der Gerechtigkeit, 1962 (Box 5 (3.2.77-Reviews by Erich Hula), Folder 131)
      - Coste, René Le Problème du Droit de Guerre dans la Pensée de Pie XII, 1963 (Box 5 (3.2.77-Reviews by Erich Hula), Folder 132)
      - Kaufmann, Erich.Der Staat in der Rechtsgemeinschaft der Völker, 1963 (Box 5 (3.2.77-Reviews by Erich Hula), Folder 133)
      - Christian Ethics and Nuclear Warfare. Ed. Ulrich S. Allers and William V. O'Brien, 1964 (Box 5 (3.2.77-Reviews by Erich Hula), Folder 134)
      - Clute, Robert E.The International Legal Status of Austria 1938-1955, 1964 (Box 5 (3.2.77-Reviews by Erich Hula), Folder 135)
      - Lador-Lederer, J.J.International Non-Governmental Organizations and Economic Entities. A Study in Autonomous Organizations and Jus Gentium, 1964 (Box 5 (3.2.77-Reviews by Erich Hula), Folder 136)
      - Reibstein, Ernst.Völkerrecht. Eine Geschichte seiner Ideen in Lehre und Praxis, 1965 (Box 5 (3.2.77-Reviews by Erich Hula), Folder 137)
      - Inhalt, Wesen und gegenwärtige praktische Bedeutung des Selbstbestimmungsrechte der Völker. Vorträge und Aussprachen. Ed. Kurt Rabl, 1965 (Box 5 (3.2.77-Reviews by Erich Hula), Folder 138)
      - Herberichs, Gérard.Théorie de la Paix Selon Pie XII, 1965 (Box 5 (3.2.77-Reviews by Erich Hula), Folder 139)
      - Huter, Franz (ed.).Suedtirol. Eine Frage des Europäischen Gewissens, 1966 (Box 5 (3.2.77-Reviews by Erich Hula), Folder 140)
      - "Carl Schmitt's Concept of the Political", 1966 (Box 5 (3.2.77-Reviews by Erich Hula), Folder 141)
      - Spengler, Erhard.Zur Frage des völkerrechtlich-gültigen Zustandekommens der deutsch-tschechoslowakischen Grenzenregelung von 1938, 1968 (Box 5 (3.2.77-Reviews by Erich Hula), Folder 142)
      - Plessow, Utta.Neutralität und Assoziation mit der EWG. Dargestellt am Beispiel der Schweiz, Schwedens und Österreichs, 1968 (Box 5 (3.2.77-Reviews by Erich Hula), Folder 143)
      - Black, Cyril E., Richard A. Falk, Klaus Knorr, Oran R. Young.Neutralization and World Politics, 1969 (Box 5 (3.2.77-Reviews by Erich Hula), Folder 144)
      - Randelzhofer, Albrecht.Völkerrechtliche Aspekte des Heiligen Römischen Reiches nach 1648, 1971 (Box 5 (3.2.77-Reviews by Erich Hula), Folder 145)
      - Rabl, Kurt.Die Völkerrechtsgrundlagen der Modernen Friedensordnung, 1971 (Box 5 (3.2.77-Reviews by Erich Hula), Folder 146)
      - Jahrbuch für Internationales Recht, 1973 (Box 5 (3.2.77-Reviews by Erich Hula), Folder 147)
      - Rabl, Kurt.Das Selbstbestimmungsrecht der Völker, 1975 (Box 5 (3.2.77-Reviews by Erich Hula), Folder 148)
      - Thompson, Kenneth W.American Diplomacy and Emerging Patterns, 1983 (Box 5 (3.2.77-Reviews by Erich Hula), Folder 149)
      - "[Kenneth] Thompson on Toynbee", 1984 (Box 5 (3.2.77-Reviews by Erich Hula), Folder 150)
  - The Washington Center of Foreign Policy Research. Round Table Meetings, September 26, 1957-September 27, 1958; 3.3; 29 file folders
    This sub-series contains transcripts of Round Table meetings of the Washington Center of Foreign Policy Research from September 1957 until September 1958. Participants include Arnold Wolfers, Roger Hilsman, James E. King Jr., Paul H. Nitze, William Lee Miller, Hans Speier, Erich Hula, Herbert S. Dinerstein, Charles Burton Marshall, William Welch, Klaus Mehnert, Hans Morgenthau and Robert C. Good. Also included in this section are typescripts of lectures delivered by Hula, Wolfers, and Miller and a limited amount of correspondence between Hula, Wolfers and Miller.
    Participants: Arnold Wolfers, Roger Hilsman, James E. King Jr., Paul H. Nitze, William Lee Miller, Hans Speier, Erich Hula, Herbert S. Dinerstein, Charles Burton Marshall, William Welch, Klaus Mehnert, Hans Morgenthau and Robert C. Good).
    - Correspondence between Hula and Arnold Wolfers, William Lee Miller, 1958; 1962 (Box 5 (3-Published and Unpublished Writings by ), Folder 151)
    - Round table meeting, 1957 September 26 (Box 5 (3-Published and Unpublished Writings by ), Folder 152)
      Wolfers.
    - Round table meeting, 1957 October 01 (Box 5 (3-Published and Unpublished Writings by ), Folder 153)
      Wolfers, Hilsman, King, Nitze, Miller.
    - Round table meeting, 1957 October 10 (Box 5 (3-Published and Unpublished Writings by ), Folder 154)
      Hula, Nitze, Miller, Wolfers, Hilsman.
    - Round table meeting, 1957 October 15 (Box 5 (3-Published and Unpublished Writings by ), Folder 155)
      Nitze.
    - Round table meeting, 1957 October 24 (Box 5 (3-Published and Unpublished Writings by ), Folder 156)
      Hula, Miller, Nitze, Hilsman, Wolfers, King.
    - Round table meeting, 1957 October 31 (Box 5 (3-Published and Unpublished Writings by ), Folder 157)
      Speier, King, Hula, Wolfers, Miller.
    - Round table meeting, 1957 November 07 (Box 5 (3-Published and Unpublished Writings by ), Folder 158)
      King, Wolfers, Marshall, Hilsman.
    - Round table meeting, 1957 November 21 (Box 5 (3-Published and Unpublished Writings by ), Folder 159)
      Miller, Nitze, Wolfers, Hilsman, Hula, King, Marshall.
    - Round table meeting, 1957 December 05 (Box 5 (3-Published and Unpublished Writings by ), Folder 160)
      Dinerstein, Hilsman, Wolfers, Miller.
    - Round table meeting, 1957 December 10 (Box 5 (3-Published and Unpublished Writings by ), Folder 161)
      Hula, Wolfers, Hilsman, Marshall.
    - Round table meeting, 1958 January 07 (Box 5 (3-Published and Unpublished Writings by ), Folder 162)
      Wolfers, King, Nitze, Marshall, Hilsman.
    - Round table meeting, 1958 January 16 (Box 5 (3-Published and Unpublished Writings by ), Folder 163)
      Nitze, Hilsman, Wolfers, King, Hula, Marshall, Bull.
    - Round table meeting, 1958 January 23 (Box 5 (3-Published and Unpublished Writings by ), Folder 164)
      Marshall, Hula, Hilsman, Wolfers, Miller, King, Bull, Nitza.
    - Round table meeting, 1958 February 04 (Box 5 (3-Published and Unpublished Writings by ), Folder 165)
      Miller, Marshall, Wolfers, Hula, Nitze, Hilsman, Welch.
    - Round table meeting, 1958 February 12 (Box 5 (3-Published and Unpublished Writings by ), Folder 166)
      Welch, Miller, Wolfers, King, Hilsman, Nitze.
    - Round table meeting, 1958 February 25 (Box 5 (3-Published and Unpublished Writings by ), Folder 167)
      Wolfers, Nitze, King, Miller, Thompson, Hula, Hilsman, Welch.
    - Round table meeting, 1958 March 14 (Box 5 (3-Published and Unpublished Writings by ), Folder 168)
      Nitze, Marshall, Welch, Hilsman, Wolfers, Miller, King.
    - Round table meeting, 1958 March 18 (Box 5 (3-Published and Unpublished Writings by ), Folder 169)
      Wolfers, Hula, Marshall, Miller, Nitze, King, Welch, Hilsman.
    - Round table meeting, 1958 April 24 (Box 5 (3-Published and Unpublished Writings by ), Folder 170)
      Nitze, Wolfers, Hula, Marshall, King, Miller.
    - Round table meeting, 1958 May 01 (Box 5 (3-Published and Unpublished Writings by ), Folder 171)
      Mehnert, Wolfers, Nitze, Hilsman, King, Hula, Marshall.
    - Round table meeting, 1958 May 02 (Box 5 (3-Published and Unpublished Writings by ), Folder 172)
      Mehnert, Wolfers, Hula, King, Welch.
    - Round table meeting, 1958 May 22 (Box 5 (3-Published and Unpublished Writings by ), Folder 173)
      Wolfers, King, Miller, Welch, Hilsman.
    - Round table meeting, 1958 June 05 (Box 5 (3-Published and Unpublished Writings by ), Folder 174)
      Marshall, Hula, Wolfers, Nitze, Kng, Hilsman, Miller.
    - Round table meeting, 1958 September 27 (Box 5 (3-Published and Unpublished Writings by ), Folder 175)
      Wolfers, Hilsman, Morgenthau, Nitze, King, Miller, Good.
    - Wolfers, Arnold. "De Gaulle's Prospective Foreign Policy and the United States. A Memorandum", 1958 June 04 (Box 5 (3-Published and Unpublished Writings by ), Folder 176)
    - Miller, William Lee. "An Interpretive Summary of the Consultation on 'Moral Responsibility and Nuclear Space Problems' of the National Council of Churches", 1958 March 06 (Box 5 (3-Published and Unpublished Writings by ), Folder 177)
    - Hula, Erich. "Flexible Law - Inflexible Ideology", Undated (Box 5 (3-Published and Unpublished Writings by ), Folder 178)
    - Hula, Erich. "The Question of Russian Objectives", Undated (Box 5 (3-Published and Unpublished Writings by ), Folder 179)
- Course and lecture notes, 4; 29 file folders
  This series contains primarily handwritten lecture and research notes, including a number of folders pertaining to the revision of the United Nations Charter.
  - Diplomacy, Undated (Box 6 (4-Course and lecture notes), Folder 1)
  - Examinations, 1966-1975 (Box 6 (4-Course and lecture notes), Folder 2)
  - Hans Kelsen, Undated (Box 6 (4-Course and lecture notes), Folder 3)
  - International Labor Organization, Undated (Box 6 (4-Course and lecture notes), Folder 4)
  - International Law, Undated (Box 6 (4-Course and lecture notes), Folder 5-6)
  - International Law and Organizations, Undated (Box 6 (4-Course and lecture notes), Folder 7)
  - International Law and the U.N., Undated (Box 6 (4-Course and lecture notes), Folder 8)
  - International Organizations, Undated (Box 6 (4-Course and lecture notes), Folder 9-10)